A Guide to the Governor Gerald L. Baliles Executive Papers, 1986-1990
Library of Virginia
- Series III. 1988 (accession 33702)
  Notable records include 1988 Annual Report of the Southern Growth Policies Board which Governor Baliles chaired and minutes of Second Quarter Executive Meeting in Washington, D.C. on 14 March 1988 (Associations, Southern Growth Policies Board, Box 96, Folder 3); minutes (12 August 1988, 10 June 1988, 6 May 1988, 19 February 1988, and 6 November 1988) of the Potomac River Fisheries Commission, copied to Governor (Governor's Office, Potomac River Fisheries Commission, Box 103, Folder 2); memorandum to file from Meredith L. Strohm, 23 December 1988 on the Executive Mansion Wine Cellar (Governor's Office, Staff Correspondence, Box 105, Folder 6); memorandum to Hugh D. Keogh, Director, Department of Economic Development, from Andrew Fogarty, 28 September 1988, requesting documentation of Governor Baliles expenses during trade mission and attached memo dated 22 July 1988 listing Governor Baliles' expenses for his April 1988 trip to Israel (Governor's Office, Staff Correspondence, Box 106, Folder 1); Virginia Israel Commission, Report to the Governor, June 1988 (Governor's Office, Virginia Israel Commission, Box 108); copy of concept study for National Air and Space Museum Dulles Wing/Phase I, September 1985 and copy of Washington National Airport Master Plan, transmitted by Linwood Holton, Chairman of Washington Airport Authority, 17 May 1988 (Governor's Office, Washington-Dulles Airport, Box 108); memorandum to Governor Baliles from Curry A. Roberts, 5 August 1988, providing a progress report on the creation of the new Department of World Trade (Cabinet, Secretary of Economic Development, Box 112, Folder 1); minutes (16 December 1987, 27 January 1988, and 24 February 1988) of Virginia Health Services Cost Review Council (Cabinet, Secretary of Health and Human Resources, Department of Rehabilitation Services, Box 124, Folder 1); and bi-weekly status reports to Governor Baliles on the new Virginia lottery from Kenneth W. Thorsen (Independent State Agencies, Lottery Department, Box 135).
  - Sub-Series A: General Correspondence
    - Acid Rain (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - AIDS (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Chesapeake Bay - General (part one) (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Chesapeake Bay - General (part two) (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Child Care (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Clean Air/Smoking (part one) (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Clean Air/Smoking (part two) (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Drug and Alcohol Abuse (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Drunk Driving (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Education (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Flag Requests (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Food Tax (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Gypsy Moth (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - High Occupancy Vehicles (HOV) (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Horse Center (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Infant Mortality (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - International Children's Festival (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Mules (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Pari-Mutuel Betting (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Poplar Forest (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Railroads/Railways - General (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - School Children's Letters (samples) (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Scouts - Boy/Eagle/Girl (part one) (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Scouts - Boy/Eagle/Girl (part two) (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Seat Belts (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Speed Limit (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - State Song (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Swan Letters (samples) (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Taxes - General (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Unanswered Letters (samples) (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series B: Associations
    - General (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - National Governors' Association - Correspondence (part one) (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - National Governors' Association - Correspondence (part two) (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - National Governors' Association - Correspondence (part three) (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - National Governors' Association - Correspondence (part four) (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - National Governors' Association - New Governor's Conference (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - [See Series VI. Miscellaneous for additional National Governors' Association records.]
    - Southern Governors' Association - Correspondence (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board (part one) (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board (part two) (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board (part three) (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board (part four) (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Southern States Energy Board - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series C: Localities
    - Cities - General (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Cities - Richmond (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Cities - Virginia Beach (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Counties - General (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Towns - General (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series D: Governor's Office
    - Bicentennial of the U.S. Constitution (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Budget (part one) (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Budget (part two) (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Commission on Excellence in Education (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Community Action Agencies (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Congratulations - Birthday (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Congratulations - General (part one) (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Congratulations - General (part two) (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Congratulations - Wedding (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Correspondence - See Staff Correspondence
    - Fishing Tournament - Bass Masters (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Geography Awareness Week (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Get Well Letters (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1988 December 27-November 2 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1988 November 1-September 9 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1988 September 7-July 25 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1988 July 22-June 17 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1988 June 16-May 26 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1988 May 25-May 10 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1988 May 9-April 18 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1988 April 15-April 4 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1988 March 31-March 8 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1988 March 7-February 16 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1988 February 15-February 1 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1988 January 29-January 4 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Cup Fishing Tournament (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Governors, Other States (part one) (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Governors, Other States (part two) (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Governors, Other States (part three) (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Grants (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Granville P. Meade Scholarship Trust (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Greetings (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Information (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - International Education (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Invitations (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Mail Trends (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Meetings and Conventions, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - [Possible] Meetings and Conventions, 1990-1994 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Messages from the Governor, 1988 January-April (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Messages from the Governor, 1988 May-August (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Messages from the Governor, 1988 September-December (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, A-D (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, E-I (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, J-N (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, O-Y (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Proclamations (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Mid-Valley Work Week (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Model General Assembly - YMCA (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Other State Offices (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Peninsula Work Week (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Potomac River Fisheries Commission (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Requests - Auction (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Requests - Contribution (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Requests - General (part one) (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Requests - General (part two) (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Resignation (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Retirement Letters (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - School for the Gifted (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Secretaries of State Conference, Norfolk, 18 December 1987 (1988 Correspondence) (See Also Box 61, Folder 1) (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Staff Correspondence (Constituent Correspondence) - See Also Form Letters (Boxes 109-110)
    - Staff Correspondence (Constituent Correspondence) - 1988 December 29-October 21 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Staff Correspondence (Constituent Correspondence) - 1988 October 20-August 5 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Staff Correspondence (Constituent Correspondence) - 1988 August 4-June 21 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Staff Correspondence (Constituent Correspondence) - 1988 June 20-May 27 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Staff Correspondence (Constituent Correspondence) - 1988 May 26-May 9 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Staff Correspondence (Constituent Correspondence) - 1988 May 6-April 25 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Staff Correspondence (Constituent Correspondence) - 1988 April 22-April 6 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Staff Correspondence (Constituent Correspondence) - 1988 April 5-March 18 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Staff Correspondence (Constituent Correspondence) - 1988 March 16-March 1 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Staff Correspondence (Constituent Correspondence) - 1988 February 29-February 3 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Staff Correspondence (Constituent Correspondence) - 1988 February 2-January 20 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Staff Correspondence (Constituent Correspondence) - 1988 January 19-January 4 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Staff Correspondence - General, 1988 December 29-October 18 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Staff Correspondence - General, 1988 October 17-August 17 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Staff Correspondence - General, 1988 August 16-July 6 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Staff Correspondence - General, 1988 July 5-June 28 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Staff Correspondence - General, 1988 June 15-May 6 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Staff Correspondence - General, 1988 May 4-April 15 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Staff Correspondence - General, 1988 April 14-March 3 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Staff Correspondence - General, 1988 March 1-February 1 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Staff Correspondence - General, 1988 January 29-January 4 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - State Fair (Atlantic Rural Exposition) (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - State of the Commonwealth Address Correspondence (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Sympathy Letters (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Thank You Letters to and from the Governor, 1988 December 23-July 1 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Thank You Letters to and from the Governor, 1988 June 30-January 11 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Thank You Letters from the Governor to the Commission on Transportation in the 21st Century (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Cultural Laureates (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Virginia International Trade Commission (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Virginia-Israel Commission (part one) (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Virginia-Israel Commission (part two) (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Virginia-Israel Commission (part three) (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Commission (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Silver Star Foundation (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Washington-Dulles Airport (part one) (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Washington-Dulles Airport (part two) (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Welcome Letters (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Work Week - See Peninsula Work Week
    - Form Letters 88-2 thru 12 (samples of) (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Form Letters 88-13 thru 24 (samples of) (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Form Letters 88-25 thru 32 (samples of) (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Form Letters 88-33 thru 44 (samples of) (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Form Letters 88-45 thru 50 (samples of) (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Form Letters 88-51 thru 61 (samples of) (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Form Letters 88-62 thru 74 (samples of) (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Form Letters 88-75 thru 80 (samples of) (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Form Letters 88-81 thru 90 (samples of) (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series E: Cabinet
    - E.1 - Secretary of Administration
    - Correspondence and Memorandums to Governor's Office, 1988 December 21-October 20 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums to Governor's Office, 1988 October 12-May 25 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums to Governor's Office, 1988 May 24-January 11 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Division of Selected Agency, Support Services (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Nurses Salaries (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Prescription Drugs (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - E.1 - Secretary of Administration - State Agencies
    - Department of General Services (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Department of Information Technology (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Department of Personnel and Training (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Department of Personnel and Training - Charitable Campaign (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Department of Personnel and Training - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (E.E.O.C.) (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Department of Veterans' Affairs (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - State Board of Elections (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - E.2 - Secretary of Economic Development
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 December 2-June 30 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 June 28-January 7 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Correspondence (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Correspondence - Economic Development, 1988 December 31-September 2 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Correspondence - Economic Development, 1988 September 1-January 4 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - E.2 - Secretary of Economic Development - State Agencies
    - Commission for the Arts (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services (part one) (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services (part two) (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services -Drought (part one) (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services -Drought (part two) (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Department of Commerce (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Department of Economic Development - Correspondence (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Department of Economic Development - Japan-Virginia Society (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Department of Economic Development - Southeast United States/Korea (SEUS/Korea), Economic Council Conference, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1988 November 13-15 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Department of Economic Development - Southeast United States/Korea (SEUS/Korea), Annual Meeting, Charleston, South Carolina, 1988 October 19-21 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Department of Economic Development - Small Business Financing Authority (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Department of Economic Development - Taiwan Trip (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Department of Economic Development - Division of Tourism (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Department of Economic Development - Virginia Film Office (part one) (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Department of Economic Development - Virginia Film Office (part two) (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Department of Forestry (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Department of Housing and Community Development (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Department of Labor and Industry (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Department of Mines, Minerals and Energy (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Department of Minority Business Enterprise (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Department of World Trade (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Southwest Virginia Economic Development Commission (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Employment Commission (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - E.2 - Secretary of Economic Development - Economic Development Topics
    - Appalachian Regional Commission (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - E.3 - Secretary of Education
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 November 9-June 10 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 May 9-January 5 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Correspondence, 1988 December 20-June 1 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Correspondence, 1988 May 31-January 13 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Correspondence (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - E.3 - Secretary of Education - Colleges and Universities
    - General (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - State Council of Higher Education (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Christopher Newport College (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - George Mason University (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - James Madison University (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Longwood College (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Mary Washington College (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Medical College of Virginia - See Virginia Commonwealth University
    - Norfolk State University (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Old Dominion University (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Old Dominion University - Virginia Center for World Trade (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Radford University (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - University of Virginia (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University/Medical College of Virginia (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Community College System (VCCS) (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Military Institute (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Virginia State University (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - College of William and Mary (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - E.3 - Secretary of Education - Education Topics
    - Board of Regents of Gunston Hall (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Commonwealth Conference on International Education (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Education Commission of the States (ECS) (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Family Life (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Museum of American Frontier Culture (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - National Student/Parent Mock Election (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Project Discovery (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Southeastern Universities Research Assoc., Inc. (SURA)/Continuous Electronic Beam Accelerator Facility (CEBAF) (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Southern Regional Education Board (SREB) (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - State Board of Education (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Scholars Program (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - E.3 - Secretary of Education - State Agencies
    - Department of Education (part one) (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Department of Education (part two) (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Department of Education (part three) (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - The Science Museum of Virginia (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - State Education Assistance Authority (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Educational Loan Authority (VELA) (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Virginia State Library and Archives (part one) (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Virginia State Library and Archives (part two) (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Virginia State Library and Archives (part three) (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - E.4 - Secretary of Finance
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 December 22-October 20 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 September 30-January 18 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Budget Correspondence (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Constituent Correspondence (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Governor's Correspondence (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - E.4 - Secretary of Finance - State Agencies
    - Department of Accounts - Comptroller (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Department of Accounts - Prompt Payment Act (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Department of Planning and Budget (part one) (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Department of Planning and Budget (part two) (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Department of Taxation (part one) (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Department of Taxation (part two) (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Department of Taxation (part three) (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Department of Taxation (part four) (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Treasury (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Treasury - Division of Unclaimed Property (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - E.5 - Secretary of Health and Human Resources (Name Change as of 1988 July 1)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 December 23-October 13 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 September 20-June 14 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 June 9-January 6 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Constituent Correspondence, 1988 December 28-August 4 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Constituent Correspondence, 1988 August 3-April 19 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Constituent Correspondence, 1988 April 8-January 7 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Correspondence (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - E.5 - Secretary of Health and Human Resources - State Agencies (Name Change as of 1988 July 1)
    - Department for the Aging (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Department for Children (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Department for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Department of Health (part one) (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Department of Health (part two) (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Certificate of Public Need - See Topics
    - Department of Health Regulatory Boards (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Department of Medical Assistance Services (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Department of Rehabilitative Services (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Department for the Rights of the Disabled (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Department of Social Services (part one) (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Department of Social Services (part two) (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Department of Social Services (part three) (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Department of Social Services (part four) (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Department of Social Services (part five) (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Department for the Visually Handicapped (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Department for Volunteerism (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Employment and Training Department (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Employment and Training Department - Job Training Partnership Act (JTPA) (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - E .5 - Secretary of Health and Human Resources - Human Resources Topics (Name Change as of 1988 July 1)
    - Certificate of Need (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Child Abuse (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Council on Indians (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Medicaid Benefits (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Mentally Disabled (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - E.6 - Secretary of Natural Resources
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 November 29-January 5 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Constituent Correspondence, 1988 December 29-June 23 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Correspondence, 1988 June 17-January 6 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Correspondence (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - E.6 - Secretary of Natural Resources - Boards and Commissions
    - Chesapeake Executive Council (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Commission to Study Historic Preservation (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - E.6 - Secretary of Natural Resources - State Agencies
    - Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Council on the Environment (Box 126, Folder 8)